radiotuna.com 2010-06-21

# 

##  Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Tuna Media Ltd ("Tuna Media", "we", "our" or "us"), company registration number 6666607 (England and Wales), uses and protects any information that you give Tuna Media Ltd when you use this website (radiotuna.com). 

Tuna Media is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website (radiotuna.com) then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Tuna Media may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1/9/09. 

###  What we collect

We may collect the following information: 

  * name 
  * contact information including email address 
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests 
  * usage data relating to your use of this website (radiotuna.com) 
  * usage data relating to your use of this website (radiotuna.com) 

###  What we do with the information we gather 

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

  * Enabling personalised features of the website 
  * Internal record keeping. 
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services. 
  * We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. You may opt out of these emails at any time. 
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests. You may opt out of these emails at any time. 

###  Security 

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

###  How we use cookies 

A cookie is a small file that is placed on your computer's hard drive. The cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This will prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

###  Links to other websites 

Our website contains links to other websites. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over any external websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

###  Controlling your personal information 

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: 

  * Whenever you are asked to register on the website, you may indicate that you do not want the information to be used by us to contact you. 
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information to contact you, you may change your mind at any time by emailing us or clicking the ‘unsubscribe me’ link that will be present in every email we send 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. 

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please contact us. 

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
